Beast in the dark
Under your skin
String me up high
Older than sin
Another killing
For this uptown thrill
Oh what a tragedy!
Peaking out behind these
Cold stone bars
Oh won't you rescue me!
I take my face off
Beneath your radar
I can't always hide
But you could try!
Yes you could try!
Shadows in white
Blackened and bruised
You sold me a lie
With power abused
Give me one more life!
Give me one more chance
To throw it all away!
When the lightning strikes!
Bring me back to life
And throw it all away!
She's dreaming of a better man!
If I could be a better man!
You aim at the part of me that's broken
And find somewhere for you to hide
Oh my! Oh why?
Ohh!
Show me your soul and your emotion
Oh baby take a look inside
Oh my! Oh why? Oh why? Oh why?
Ehh!
Another killing
For this uptown thrill
Oh what a tragedy!
Peaking out behind these
Cold stone bars
Oh won't you rescue me!
I take my face off
Beneath your radar
I can't always hide
But you could try!
Yes you could try!
Give me one more life!
Give me one more chance
To throw it all away!
(If you want it, let's do it! Ride it! I'll hold you!)